MD Murtuj

Mob. 8750412077 mdmurtuj15@gmail.com 15/01/1996 (Age - 28) A-3 Ram Dutt Enclave Uttam Nagar New Delhi - 110059

ABOUT ME

My passion is to build on my career as a Subject Matter Expert and seek new roles that offer opportunities to learn and develop my key teaching skills. I aim to continue exploring new teaching techniques throughout my career and incorporate innovative teaching technologies in the classroom.

SKILLS & PROFICIENCIES

- Computer Specialization in MS Office
- Adaptability
- Customer Service
- Communication Skill
- Multitasking
- Problem-solving
- Work ethic
- Organizational and Time Management Skill

CERTIFICATION & VOLUNTEER WORK

- Secured "Gold Medal" in NCC ATC Camp conducted by Indian Army.
- Secured "Best student" in academic and cocurricular activities for working dedicatedly with the NGO Chhatrabandhu.
- Secured "Best Debater" in Maharaja Surajmal College.
- Secured "Second position" in Speech Competition conducted by Delhi Public Library.
- Secured "Second position" in State Level Nukkad Natak conducted by Hindi Academy, Delhi Government.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

IGNOU - MA Final Year - language & literature

SCHOOL OF OPEN LEARNING

UNIVERSITY OF DELHI - BA Political Hons.

2020 - From North Campus.

SCERT DEL.ED - DIET

2017 - Rajender Nagar

CBSE – 12th Standard -2015

RPVV Sec -10 Dwarka.

GOVT. BOYS SR SEC SCHOOL NO -2 UTTAM NAGAR

CBSE - 10TH Standard - 2013

WORK HISTORY _____

SCHOOL TEACHER

Primary Teacher - (2019 - March 2024)

To obtain a position as an elementary school teacher that will utilize my dedication to children's educational needs development.

NGO-SARD-

Master Trainer - (2017 - 2019)

Develop professional skills such as problem-solving, communication and teamwork; Build relationships with professionals in the industry; Learn about different cultures and ways of working; Make a positive impact on society by contributing to an NGO's mission.

NGO - Chhatrabandhu - 5 year

Project Manager - (2013 - 2017)

To bring my passion for helping others and strong organizational skills to fill the role of Non-Profit Manager at an established organization.

(MD Murtuj)